export const data = {
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How often do you find yourself experiencing anxiety in daily situations?",
      "options": [
        "Rarely+0",
        "Occasionally+1",
        "Frequently+2",
        "Almost always+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Rarely"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you tend to express your anxiety outwardly or keep it to yourself?",
      "options": [
        "Express outwardly+3",
        "Keep to myself+1",
        "Varies depending on the situation+2",
        "I don't experience anxiety+0"
      ],
      "correctOption": "I don't experience anxiety"
    },
    {
      "question": "What triggers your anxiety the most?",
      "options": [
        "Uncertainty+1",
        "Social situations+3",
        "Performance expectations+2",
        "Feeling threatened+0"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Feeling threatened+0"
    },
    {
      "question": "How would you describe the intensity of your anxiety when it occurs?",
      "options": [
        "Mild+0",
        "Moderate+1",
        "Severe+2",
        "Extreme+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Mild"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you actively seek methods to manage and control your anxiety?",
      "options": [
        "Yes, regularly+3",
        "Sometimes+2",
        "Rarely+1",
        "No, not at all+0"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Yes, regularly"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have others expressed concern about your anxiety behavior?",
      "options": [
        "Yes, frequently+3",
        "Occasionally+2",
        "Rarely+1",
        "No, never+0"
      ],
      "correctOption": "No, never"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you feel regret or guilt after experiencing anxiety?",
      "options": [
        "Always+0",
        "Sometimes+1",
        "Rarely+2",
        "Never+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Always"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you sought professional help or counseling for anxiety-related issues?",
      "options": [
        "Yes+0",
        "Considering it+1",
        "No, not yet+2",
        "No, and I don't plan to+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "How would you rate the impact of anxiety on your relationships and daily life?",
      "options": [
        "Low impact+0",
        "Moderate impact+1",
        "High impact+2",
        "Very high impact+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Low impact"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you believe that addressing and managing anxiety is important for overall well-being?",
      "options": [
        "Strongly agree+0",
        "Agree+1",
        "Neutral+2",
        "Disagree+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Strongly agree"
    }
  ]
}
